Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
MILLIONS OF YEARS AGO
THE AFTERNOON BEFORE LAST
Are you bored. Zoe?
Worse than bored.
Excellent.
That means the punishment is working.
What have I done to deserve this prison?
Why can't we be free. like animals?
I mean. look at that bird.
flying happily in the sky.
Because you're human. Zoe.
and humans have rules to follow.
Well. maybe being human
isn’t as cool as we think.
You know what's not cool?
The troublemaking that got you here.
Shall I remind you?
Bribing the cook. and leaving
your whole class without dessert?
Hey... It was his idea!
Breaking six windows
and causing a cold epidemic.
Windows... They're everywhere.
it’s hard not to hit them!
Clogging the teachers' bathroom
with toilet paper.
causing a flood of... You know.
No. no... No!
Proving that the pipes are old
and we're all in danger.
Excuses! I'll deny saying this. but...
Do you want to end up like Donna?
What?
Expelled from three schools.
held back six times.
is that what you want?
To be a rebel
with a phenomenal personality.
flamboyant sense of fashion
and no academic future?
Yeah! No?
You have to try to get along
with people and be polite.
You're not the only person in the world.
don't you understand?
Saved by the bell. See you later!
Hey!
One minute to save the planet?
Hi there!
Have you heard of Greenbuddies?
We're an environmental organization
fighting to protect the planet from...
Hello! One minute to save the planet?
Hey. you.
My parents forgot to pack me
my lunch this morning.
Again? No!
A big guy like you
needs lots of energy.
Here. why don’t you take...
And my grandmother
just had an operation.
I could use some money
for a ride to the hospital.
Poor woman.
she never catches a break.
Here. why don’t you take my card?
The PIN number is 4-1-2...
...2-7. I know.
Excuse you.
Out of my way. brat.
Seriously. Kyle. Set boundaries.
Boundaries? Where?
Hey. have you thought about volunteering
for Greenbuddies yet?
I emailed you this month's
recycling workshops.
-Did you see them? Did ya?
-No.
Well the park clean-up
is this afternoon.
-Are you coming?
-No.
Did you see my model of the Arctic?
-Did you?
-No!
I made it with my Aunt Ronnie.
It represents how in an ecosystem
living beings
and the place where they live
give and receive equally.
forming a balance that...
Zoe?
I almost forgot!
Just for considering volunteering.
I've got this exclusive pin for you.
Kyle. I said... Aaarrggh!
How many times do I have to tell you
to leave me alone?
I don't care about any of this!
xxx
Oh no! Fire!
Aarghh!
Zoeee!
I'm just asking you
to look at the map.
Because the satellites
are showing activity
in an area
that should be uninhabited!
Nothing has survived there
for years!
Do I have to explain
global warming to you?
The animals should have migrated!
Something made them stay!
Don't touch that!
Of course I'm still here!
It's a laboratory. things explode!
According to my measurements
there is a primal force there
and my theory is that it connects to...
Are you ready?
The origin of life.
If I could prove it.
it wouldn't be a theory.
But I will soon.
as soon as my samples arrive... Ah!
What do I care about your time?
I don't want your time.
I want your money!
Don't you...
I'm very calm!
When I have the samples
and confirm my theory.
your university will be begging
to fund this expedition!
And you'll be the crazy one!
Useless paper pushers!
Why doesn't anyone understand me?
It's just mutagenic biomolecular botany!
It's not like it's quantum neuronuclear
thermophysics. for crying out loud.
And as for you guys...
Zoe!
Hello!
-Oh. there you are.
-Why aren't they in their cage?
Poor things. Does the mean lady
want to lock you up?
Okay. Rufus.
Blinky
and Womby.
Aww. you’re so good.
Aren't they adorable?
They're a hazard.
that’s what they are.
Take them away and don't bother me
unless someone knocks on the door.
I'm waiting for some samples.
It's your teacher. What does he want?
Hello?
You burnt down the school?!
Just a hallway.
And it was an accident. Kinda.
Excuses. This time you've gone too far.
You're grounded!
Oh. really? Wow...
One week without your tablet!
No tablet.
No phone for a month!
And no phone. anything else?
A year. without going out!
Mom. let's be honest.
As soon as you get back to the lab
you'll forget all about this
and Dad's about to come
and pick me up. so...
Why don't we just go ahead
and ignore each other
like we always seem to do?
I said no phone. That’s no joke.
It’s one thing to not make
anything out of yourself.
but it’s another
to endanger your classmates.
How about finishing school at...
The academy of Standhaftigkeitt.
What?
A boarding school?!
You can't be serious!
Oh. no? Watch me sign you up.
No! Please. I'll behave!
That’s up to you.
Another call from school
and this goes straight into the mail.
As much as it pains me.
your education is more important than...
My samples!
Peggy!
Gordon...
Dad!
Mom wants to send me
to boarding school!
To boarding school?
That’s great!
It’s great?
Sure! Like camp.
just all year round. right?
It's not a camp.
it's where they teach discipline
to lost causes like her.
Your daughter burned down the school!
No. just a hallway...
I just think we're all
a little nervous.
Let's relax.
take a deep breath
and focus on what's important.
Did I leave my paddle racket here?
It's in the umbrella stand.
Perfect.
Huh?
No! Get off!
Why do they always
have to climb on me like this?
For some scientifically
inexplicable reason. they like you.
Well. I don't like them.
Damn vermin...
They're exotic animals.
Exotic?!
What's so special
about this creature.
-may I ask?
-It's a wombat.
The only animal in the world
that poops square poop.
You should have left them
in the laboratory
where you found them...
-Square poops. for real?
-I swear.
-Can we get back on topic here?
-What topic?
Your daughter burned down the school!
It was just a hallway!
Don't yell!
Was anyone hurt?
No! Nobody!
Well don't make a big deal
out of it. Peggy.
It's just kids stuff.
What kind of father are you?
For you. anything comes before...
My samples!
Fascinating!
She's grounded. no phone.
no tablet and no going out.
have fun!
Wait a minute. is it my turn?
I have a game with the legal guys.
Why do you think
I came to get the racket?
Well I have to analyze. process.
and catalog these samples.
so you tell me.
I say... heads.
Then I’m tails.
Oh. darn it!
And you. Zoe. not a sound!
Dad...
Yes. sweetheart. I’m listening.
I don't want to go to boarding school.
Love you too. Bye.
xxx
It can't be... Robert.
Robert!
The samples you brought show
an ultra-complex mutagenic conglomerate
that acts on genomes by altering
their cellular structure.
Isn't that fascinating?
These berries have some effect
on the animals that eat them.
but what exactly?
First of all.
where did they come from?
They don't resemble anything
that exists on our planet.
so that means they must be...
extraterrestrial?
I'm going to win the Nobel!
Did you hear that Robert?
The Oscar for educated people.
The Nobel Prize!
Calm down. calm down.
I’ll need a Moleculoscope.
Will they let me borrow one
from the university?
Better not to ask.
Let's get this show on the road!
I'll need a new lab coat
when I collect the prize...
Hmm... Heels or flats...?
I'm leaving. Don't go into the lab!
I want my phone back.
No phone!
And if your teacher calls me
for any reason...
Then you go straight
to boarding school.
Got it?!
Ugh! Why are your toys
scattered all over the house?
Pick them up. will you?
They’re not what you think they are...
Agh!
Just don't go in the laboratory!
As if breaking down
genomes wasn't enough.
now I have to deal with
geometric excrements.
If you think I'm going through life
without a cell phone.
you're crazy.
xxx
Aha!
You're so predictable. Mom...
Oww! Ouch!
Oh. wow.
Robert will have some work
when he wakes up.
You’re getting hair all over everything.
Hey! Stop that!
Okay. that's better.
Oh. these blue ones are new.
Rufus.
Blinky
and Womby.
And this one's for me.
Yuck. it tastes like real fruit.
What were they thinking?
Okay. this isn't very...
...normal.
Woah! What was that?
Guys?
Oh. no... Rufus!
-Rufus?
-Aaahh!
Rufus.
-Womby!
-Womby?
Blinky?
Blinky!
-Rufus!
-Womby!
Blinky!
-Rufus.
-Blinky.
Womby
-Rufus.
-Blinky.
Womby
Rufus. Blinky. Womby
Rufus. Blinky. Womby!
You can talk?!
-So you can talk?
-So you can talk!
OK. I admit this is super cute.
But what happened?
Ayayay...
I've really messed up now.
Forgive me for this. guys.
Enough already!
It'll only be while I'm at school!
I need you to be quiet
and stay put
or the mean lady
will lock you up forever.
understood?
Enough!
If I'm late
Mr. Ramirez will call.
and if he calls...
Think. think. think...
What did Mom and Dad do
when I acted like this?
Hello. boys and girls!
Today we're going to learn
about the alphabet.
Are you ready? Here we go!
Let’s begin at the beginning
with the letter A.
Here are all of the words
that begin with the letter A.
Anemone. acquaintance.
astrolabe. amphibian...
It's addictive. isn't it?
Behave yourselves!
...Atom. agenda. alarm.
amphora. agile.
acid. avocado. anchor.
America. Australia.
automobile. architecture. art.
astronomy. airport. angel...
Okay. I made it.
The bus should be here...
Huh? Oh. no!
Open up! Please. I'm begging you!
I love it when this happens.
No. At the bus stop.
What do you want.
for me to get on my knees?
Alright. I'll get on my knees.
Open up. please!
You can get on at the next stop!
You think that's funny?
Oh yeah. real funny.
So long...
Maybe now
you’ll start showing up on time.
I know where you live!
I know where you buy your bread!
Hey!
Ahh!
What’s going on?
-How did you...?
-Ahh!
Oh my God!
Thank a lot!
Good morning. people.
Thank God it’s Friday!
Olga. how's the renovation going?
Great? Glad to hear it.
Amelia?
Those sneakers are awesome!
Welcome to SheetCorp.
the humble sheet factory that.
thanks to a mixture of foresight
and savage turbo-capitalism.
became the Mega Company
it is today.
Advanced technology
and prohibitive prices.
All so our consumers believe
they're better than they really are.
In the words of our new CEO.
Timothy Johnson...
Evolution?
Nature has already taken us
as far as it can on it’s own.
But don't worry.
the next step is on me.
Great game yesterday. huh?
You're a real champ!
Ah... Now we’re talking...
Ready for another gruelling day
on the job.
Am I bothering you?
Yes! I mean. no!
I mean. hey!
Come on in.
give me a second to...
finish up...
there we go...
Mr. Johnson!
Hashtag meeting my team.
hashtag cool boss.
Let's see those likes.
Now we’re talking.
Gordon Frink.
Mr President!
You can call me TJ.
Of course. TJ.
Can I get you anything?
Some chips. a soda...
No. I'm sticking with
my protein shake.
This marble won't sculpt itself.
you know?
Are they all yours? Just kidding.
I love animals. and your daughter!
She seems lovely.
You should bring her in sometime.
Of course. That’s a great idea.
So I'm actually talking to
the inventor of the Calcu-clock.
It was a true revolution.
the work of an absolute genius.
Well. that was many years ago...
Yes. Way too many.
And since then... nothing.
Are you sure you don't want...
anything?
For you to do your job.
Sorry. did I make you
feel uncomfortable?
That wasn’t my intention at all.
No. not at all!
I'm so comfortable!
I see.
Maybe a little too comfortable.
Gordon.
SheetCorp has been giving you more
than you’ve been giving back
for a long time.
But that ends today.
Before this day is over.
you're going to bring me an idea.
Something brilliant.
something that will advance humanity.
And if not...
If not...?
If not. then you are out.
But that's not going to happen
to a genius like you. right?
-Get to work!
-Get to work?
Get to work?!
Alright. I'm a normal girl
going to have a normal day.
I'm not going to break anything.
or flood anything or...
Hey. Zoe.
Are you going
to burn anything today?
Do you take requests?
What's wrong with her now?
She should be locked up!
Okay. okay.
You're nervous about boarding school.
that's normal.
but you've got everything
under control.
Calm down.
think of something else.
Look. there's Donna.
Wow. she’s so cool...
She even chews gum with style.
I wish I knew
how to chew like that.
Do you think
you can teach meaaoww...
Excuse me.
Don't do that. Okay?
Sorry.
I was checking the pavement.
Solid and levelled.
just the way I like it.
See you in class. toodles.
Toodles?
Who are you trying to fool?
It's those blue things!
They've transformed
your animals and you too.
-but into what?
-Zoe!
I’m totally fine!
Oh. okay. That is awesome.
Want to help sort the trash?
That's the janitor's job.
I know.
He asked me to help him.
He had to get his haircut.
But he's bald!
Never mind.
Hey. I wanted to say sorry.
Sorry? For what?
For yelling at you
and burning your model.
Oh. that!
It's okay. don’t worry about it.
You must have had a real rough day.
Like my Aunt Ronnie always says:
patience and kindness
put violence behind us.
Oh Kyle. you're either
too nice or too naive.
One of the two.
Oh! Thanks?
Have you thought
about volunteering yet?
I have an application here.
I just need your signature.
I already told you...
So is that a yes?
Not now. Kyle.
OK. so. later then?
Yes. later!
Later...
And with that we finish
the past perfect subjunctive.
What are you doing?
Don't pause it!
Why’d you pause it?
Cause it's over.
Over? Woah. it was like...
Boom! Right?
Wasn't it like boom. Blinky?
Womby! Wasn't it like boom?
Not bad. What else is there?
It’s all here.
Anything you want.
Wow. really?
That is so cool. Super cool!
I'm starving. is anyone else hungry?
Womby. are you hungry?
I could always eat.
But did you forget?
We're locked in a cage here!
I know what to do.
Suzie. how to open a
pet cage from the inside.
Showing results for
'opening a pet cage from the inside'.
Oh my!
This Suzie is the best!
Truly amazing.
Will anything bad happen if we go out?
Zoe seemed worried
when she put us in there.
I mean. we did speak Human.
she could have just told us
what to do.
Hey. guys! I have got a great idea.
you're going to love it!
We can leave like this.
or better yet.
we can do it with style.
Ha!
What?
You can. it's totally you.
Isn't it totally him. Blinky?
If going out
without underwear is his thing.
then yes. it's totally him.
We’ve been naked all our lives
and now there’s a dress code?
A little bit of sauce.
Some carrots.
Let’s close this baby up.
Is this edible?
Oops. no. not edible.
Something’s off here.
Owff? What do you bwean?
It’s dwelicious.
Yesterday.
everything seemed so simple.
Eating. sleeping.
pooping on the carpet...
But today it's all words
and thoughts and...
I don't know. Look.
This is a wombat.
doing what a Wombat is supposed to do.
And now look at this.
Whatever it is.
don't get me involved.
This isn't our place.
Then where is it? The cage?
It's not the cage is it?
Is it the cage?
No! Don't let it be the cage.
We're fine. mate.
You need to chill out
and come watch a little TV.
This isn't your place.
Oh. you’ve got to be kidding.
Something within you calls.
drives you to search.
to reach beyond.
Trust your instincts.
awaken your inner animal.
defy the status quo.
Shhh!
Find your way...
to Salvatica.
Salvatica pour homme.
That's our place!
We have to go to Salvatica!
I love it. I love it. I love it!
Womby. don't you love it?
Don't you love it?
I'm not going to argue
with what’s on the TV.
If it's baloney.
we can always come back.
We have to tell Zoe before we go.
Zoe said she had to go to school.
Suzie. how do we get to school?
Showing route to "school".
We're going to Salvática!
No one followed me. right?
Alright. Nobel. here I come!
As an adventure. it was short.
but really intense.
Just who I’ve been looking for.
Do you realize
what you did yesterday?
You're lucky Kyle covered for you.
because if not...
This book says that all animals
share some of the same DNA.
Is that true?
Zoe. have you been studying the book?
Well. is it true?
Of course! Look:
Millions of years ago.
this little fella decided
to take a trip onto land.
He put those little legs
to work right away
wanting to see
everything in the world.
And boy. did he ever!
New environment. new challenges.
new mutation.
new species.
Increasingly diverse.
Among them.
maybe not the most important
but undoubtedly
the most fashionable. us:
Homo sapiens.
So yes. it's true.
We all have evolved
from the same genetic materials.
so there is some of every animal
inside every living creature.
And what if those animals
inside of me took control?
Zoe. we're talking about
very distant genetic memories.
You have nothing to worry about.
Unless. of course.
you come into contact with
an ultra-complex mutagenic conglomerate
that acts on genomes
by altering their cellular structure.
But that's not something you typically
have lying around the house. right?
Hey there. come on in.
Alright. kids.
who can tell me the name
of this organ right here?
Anyone?
You all seem a little sleepy today.
Well. never mind.
let's move on to another organ.
What is this one called?
Here's a clue:
it's the one I need you to use
from time to time.
Alright?
Come on. any volunteer?
Zoe?!
Get back to your seat now!
I'm sorry!
It’s out of my control!
Let’s get back to our lesson.
Your classmates are not to blame.
for your lack of self-control.
Mom. I'm scared!
I want to go home!
Try giving it a turn...
What do you think I’m doing?
This is making me nuts.
Forget it.
Psst! Come here!
Over there.
Bingo! Let's go!
Robert?
As a scientist. I shouldn't
believe in magic. you know?
But this is the closest thing
to magic I've ever seen.
I still don't know how it's possible.
this compound allows the genes
of any living being
to turn into any other.
If I could control that.
the applications would be endless.
What am I saying. endless?
They would be infinite!
Infinite might be a stretch.
you know I like to stay within...
I feel like something salty.
Robert! Bring me some peanuts!
Robert?
Robert! Are you deaf?
I asked you to bring me some peanuts!
Ugh. peanuts.
How hard can that be?
Agh! Grounded again.
what am I going to do?
Stinky Ramírez...
A mutagenic conglomerate isn't something
you typically have around the house.
He obviously doesn't know my mother!
Hey.
I like your vibe.
My... What?
Your vibe. it's wild. Grrrr.
Come on.
I’ve got something for you to do.
Oh! Okay. um.
a cowboy hat that has speakers.
You can listen to country music
while doing cowboy stuff.
Is the cowboy thing still in?
I don’t know...
Dang it! C’mon Gordon.
you’ve got to think. think!
I know! Nightvision sunglasses!
Oh yeah. because then you
won’t need to take them off at all.
Does that even make sense?
Does it matter?
I mean. it's better than nothing.
What? Why won't you...
Stupid marker. this is all your fault!
Who am I kidding?
The only fault here is mine!
I'll never get another idea
as good as the Calcu-clock!
There’s no way!
Wait...
I think I’ll make a call today.
Robert! Answer that!
Hey there Robert! Is Peggy around?
Gordon. I'm busy.
I know. that's why I said to myself:
I should call in case she needs help.
What if you are struggling
with a new interesting project.
discovery. or invention?
Throwing ideas around with another
researcher is simply invaluable.
I mean. remember how it worked for us?
How it worked for you. you mean?
Like when I mentioned how practical
a calculator on a watch would be
and the next day you patented
a Calculator Watch that made you rich?
Come on. really?
That’s the way you remember it?
My marigolds!
Some of us are trying to work. OK?
Hey. those are great costumes!
Thanks! Right back at ya!
Jack. control yourself.
Donuts first. justice later.
I love the street!
I love the people!
Why didn't we come out sooner?
Don't you love the street?
No. it's hard on my feet and... long.
How much further to school?
According to this.
we're half an hour away.
Half an hour!
That's like 0.1% of my life!
Go on without me.
you can show me the photos later.
It says it's 6 minutes by car.
Oh! By car!
Yes. yes. yes!
I've always wanted drive in a car!
And where are we going to get a car?
Anywhere!
There's one there.
there's one there. there's one there.
Look. here's one right here.
Now connect the two cables
and the vehicle will start.
Alright! Safety first!
Womby. get on the pedals.
And you Blinky. lead the way.
-You got it!
-How do I do it? Like this?
My
macchiato
!
Who was that?
Stop right there!
The guy from before.
See you later!
Go straight. go straight.
go straight. go left!
Hey! Where are you going?!
I think the secret is to go really fast
and get out of the way for everyone
who likes driving slow.
Where did you get
your driver's license?!
There's another pedal here!
Should we see what it does?
Yeah. go for it!
[Andy]
This is the police!
Stop the vehicle!
We're losing momentum!
Go straight. go straight. go right!
Are you sure this is the way?
It’s a shortcut. keep going.
Are you sure. Blinky?
Trust me. the only way to get there
faster would be to fly...
Woah!
Give me a warning next time.
will ya?
I don't know how I did that. but okay.
That tree was not on the map.
And then they wonder
why there are accidents.
Guys. guys. guys! Look! There it is!
And in well under 6 minutes!
The name’s Chloe. right?
Zoe.
Chloe. you and I.
we haven't talked much.
but I think we have quite a lot
in common. Don't you agree?
Um. well...
People like us. we're different.
we have things to do.
we can't spend our lives stuck in here.
But here we are.
Year after year after year.
And why?
Because it's the law?
Exactly. adults and their stupid rules.
Don't they realise
the more rules they make.
the more we want to break them?
That's precisely why I need your help.
Can I count on you?
I guess so. for what?
To steal the exam we have on Monday.
Steal the exam?!
My contact in administration says
Ramirez printed them yesterday.
They're inside his briefcase.
If they catch us.
we’ll get expelled!
Uh-huh.
Whatever happens. we come out ahead.
Don't you love it?
Wow. um... I don't know.
Well I know.
Listen carefully.
I'm not going to repeat this.
I've been working
on a foolproof plan for months.
There's no room for improvisation.
understood?
-Here's what you need to do...
-Hey! Oh my gosh!
A police car just crashed
at the school gate!
What? Another disaster? Run!
Great. what now?
-Now! Go in there and get it!
-What about the plan?
Forget the plan! Move it!
Zoe! Is this later?
Kyle. this isn't a good time!
Oh. sorry!
You want to go check out the car crash?
Come on!
You can sign the form on the way over.
I have a pen here.
No. I'm going to class.
I have to...
Mr. Ramirez asked me
to keep an eye on things while he’s out.
Oh... Someone could break in
and steal something.
that’s good thinking.
Mr. Ramirez is lucky
to have someone like you.
-Like me?
-Yeah. like you.
Someone he can trust.
Zoe!
How did you track me down?
We could smell you
as soon as we got here.
You sweat a lot.
I'd have that checked.
When did you get so good at talking?
About an hour and a half.
We also learned how to use the oven.
tie a bow tie.
turn on the closed captioning.
jump-start a car and driving.
We're trusting our instincts.
that’s all.
Awakening our inner animal.
Defying the status quo.
We're going to Salvatica.
Come with us!
What are you talking about?
You can't be here!
What if someone sees you?
Do you want to get sent to a laboratory?
Well. there was some kind of crash.
or whatever.
What are you asking me for?
I was here...
Gotta go. Later!
No. no. no!
What's going on? The light!
Where's the light?
Please!
I need you to stay there quiet in there!
Come on!
Please. no! The light!
Please. come on! Don't you trust me?
-Yes!
-Yes.
Hey. whatcha doing?
Turning off the sound. just in case.
Don't turn it off!
Someone might need to call us!
Okay. I'll put it on vibrate.
Zoe. what...
What’s going on...?
Zoeee!
No!
The molecular structure
is more complex than I expected.
It's impossible to crack!
Have you considered
inverse fractal decomposition?
Of course! Huh...?
Did you...?
Wait. was that you?
You can talk?
I said... Have you considered
inverse fractal decomposition?
Oh my word!
The mixture of the compound
and the energy drink...
...has accelerated our evolution.
It's a little bit more complex
than that. but well deduced.
This proves my theory is correct.
The berries alter
the DNA of the animals!
Did you hear that. Robert?
My theory is correct!
Woo-hooo!
Reverse fractal decomposition.
here we go.
Utilizing the endoplasmic reticulum?
What else?
Finally. someone who
knows what I'm talking about.
Not now!
What did she do?
Expelled!
For stealing an exam!
What am I going to do?
Do you know how bad this is for me?
The mean lady!
-What do we do?
-Shhh.
Mom. There’s something you need to know.
I don't want to hear a word!
I hope you enjoyed
your last day of freedom
because you're going to spend
the rest of your high school days
locked up in boarding school.
I hope it's important
because I'm in big trouble...
Your daughter stole an exam!
Zoe. how could you let them catch you?
-Dad...
-That's just great.
This is your fault for raising her
to believe in the law of least effort!
-Mom...
-What do you mean my fault?
How can it be all my fault
when I hardly ever see her?
Oh. you’ll see her plenty.
She'll stay with you
until she goes to boarding school.
What? No. no. no. no.
that's terrible for me.
It would be worse for me.
-Heads.
-Tails.
Zoe. stop that nonsense right now!
Is this normal for her?
Zoe! I said to stop that!
Woah. everything's under control here!
Please forgive our friend.
she's a wee bit nervous.
Don’t worry. we were just going...
Did your rabbit just talk.
or am I going nuts?
Oh my word!
You went into my laboratory. didn’t you?
I'm not angry.
I just want to know
if you ate any of the berries
they brought me from the Arctic.
that's all.
Well. maybe one or two?
Zoe. this is...
Fascinating!
You intertwined your genetic memories!
How did it happen?
Through direct contact?
Indirect contact?
Before or after ingestion?
Did you notice anything unusual?
Sensations. sounds?
Any strange lumps?
Dad! Say something to her!
This exceeds all my expectations!
We’ll grab those cuties
and get back to the lab.
-So many tests to carry out.
-No way!
What kind of mother
experiments on their own daughter?
-Are you implying I'm a bad mother?
-Bad? You're dangerous!
-Let her go. she's coming with me!
-No. she's not!
Ah!
Stop! You’ll hurt her!
There must be
a civilized way to do this?
You know. the monkey's right.
Heads!
What? No!
Gordon!
What are we doing here?
I want to introduce you
to someone.
Yeah. well?
Come on. say something.
don't be rude.
Is there anything to eat here or what?
I'm starving. Is it just me?
What's the Wi-Fi’s password?
Are we going to be here long?
If we are.
I’d love to take my shoes off.
Oh my goodness!
We’ll get you a menu right away.
VivaPiñata_99.
And you. make yourself at home.
And you are?
I’m someone that weird stuff happens to.
It’s incredible!
You're incredible. too!
What an exotic little group.
Did you know that the wombat
is the only animal in the world
that poops square poop?
-Oh. well.
-Oh boy. do we ever.
That makes them easy to stack.
Gordon. do you think I could
talk to you for just a moment?
Guys. if you want. you can wait
over here inside the break room.
Are we really going to spend
Friday in an office?
The most bori...
...coolest place in the world!
Maybe we can wait a little while...
You're a genius. Gordon!
I knew that I could count on you.
Your daughter and her pets have had
their genetic memories intertwined.
Right? Am I right?
Yeah. something like that. y’know?
How did you do it?
With an ultra-complex
mutagenic conglomerate
that acts on genomes by altering
their cellular structure. right?
It's a complicated process.
I don't want to bore you with details.
Talking animals. yeah?
We're going to make a fortune.
Great idea. Talking pets!
That’s super.
Leave them here.
we'll take care of the marketing
and everything.
Yeah. we’ll leave them.
Wait.
I should to talk to Zoe about that.
She can stay as well!
We’ve got plenty of room.
Our company is one big happy family.
Then I should stay too?
No. you go home and rest until tomorrow.
You've earned it.
You must be exhausted
after all that effort.
Well. a little. yes.
But I still need to talk to Zoe...
I really do try my best.
but it’s just so hard. you know?
Am I a bad mother?
Why exactly?
Because I have to pay more attention
to my work than to my daughter?
I don't know.
Do you do that?
I don't know. do I?
I do!
Oh I do!
I'm a terrible mother!
The analysis!
It seems the compound
is more invasive than we had thought.
Oh no.
that means soon Zoe
will turn into an animal forever!
Unless...
Unless we find the antidote!
I may be a bad mother.
but I'm a great scientist.
Let's get to work!
One.
two.
three pizzas for free.99!
This place is high tech.
But the sofas are like
something from grandma's house.
Okay. grandma from the future!
How about a little snack?
Hey!
You wanted a snack. didn't you?
Well. snack up!
Wow! And I thought reality was wild.
Wow! Can you do that again?
Do what?
Ugh. Where's my dad?
He left. he had things to do.
Want a smoothie?
No. Great.
Abandoned with strangers.
Again.
What do you mean stranger?
I'm TJ Johnson!
Scientist. philanthropist. influencer.
Kids these days
aren’t in touch with the world.
Suzie. look up TJ Johnson.
Showing results for TJ Johnson.
TJ Johnson.
a selfless and generous leader.
...as concerned about the planet
as TJ Johnson.
When TJ Johnson's peace speech
brought tears to the eyes of...
-TJ Johnson.
I'm more into kitten videos.
Meow!
And speaking of animals.
my DNA is having a party
and I don't know how long
I'll be able to control it.
Why is it something you want to control?
What's happening to you
is called genetic mutation.
It means you're evolving.
It means you’re becoming
something unique.
I wish my parents thought like you.
They want to send me to boarding school.
Oh. I went to boarding school too.
Really? How was it?
It was horrible and traumatic.
but fine.
Got time for a flashback?
Hmm... Okay.
I'll never forget the day I got there.
My parents told me
we were going to buy yogurt.
but that was a lie.
Nobody has to packs their bags
to buy yogurt.
I was only 8 years old.
and already alone.
I tried to make friends
the only way I knew how:
by proving that
I was smarter than all of them.
But for some reason it didn't work.
I got used to the loneliness
and devoted myself
to more useful things than having fun.
I discovered my true passion: science.
I began to search
for the origin of life.
The spark that transforms
something small and fragile
into something big and powerful.
How life finds ways to thrive
under any circumstance.
No. no!
But the world wasn't made for curious.
sensitive people like me.
The world belonged to the strongest.
So I turned away from everything
and studied like no one else.
Waiting for bad weather
to make my oath as epic as possible.
and when that storm arrived...
I swore I would change everything.
I would become so strong that one day
I would rule the world!
That is. figuratively speaking.
of course.
I gotta go. but just so you know.
this isn't a boarding school.
here you can do anything you desire.
So. what are you gonna do?
Test 6007. loading simulation!
I have a good feeling about this.
I think this’ll be the one.
Aaaah! You animal!
What's going on here?
She tried to bite me!
What are you doing there?
That lamp cost a fortune...
Get down here right now!
That's no way to treat
designer furniture. Zoe!
I'm talking to you!
Look at the mess you’ve made!
Don't you growl at me. young lady!
Zoe. come!
Keep an eye on her. I'll be right back!
This is Peggy. If you're hearing this.
I'm not interested
in what you have to say.
Gordon! You're back.
What are you doing here?
Everything okay?
Zoe's a little genetically confused.
I think we should talk to her mother.
she understands this stuff.
What? No!
She's just a kid!
She's having some fun.
Relax Gordon.
And let us do our work.
What is all this?
Gordon. what did I just tell you?
This is a top-secret project.
you have no business being in here.
You're spying on my daughter!
We are studying
your daughter’s behaviour.
But why?
To find out what's going on
inside of her.
turn it into a delicious
vanilla-flavored powder
and sell it!
Just look at her!
Strength. agility. instinct...
All the qualities of the animal world
will be available to anyone.
This. Gordon.
this is the next step
in the evolution of humanity.
We didn't agree to any of this at all.
We're getting out of here right now.
Gordon. Zoe is not in danger.
I'm a scientist. not a...
Why am I wasting my time
explaining this?
Security!
Detain Gordon Frink!
No! Back! Sit!
I said. sit!
Blinky! Womby!
A little help here!
I'm trying to listen to an audiobook.
if you don't mind.
We have to do something!
This has gotten way out of hand!
Leave her alone. she's just playing.
She’s just playing?
That’s just great. perfect. wonderful.
My personal best
and I didn't get the statement!
No! No! Get down!
Bad human! Bad!
Leave her alone.
she's just playing with you.
We're getting out of here right now!
It's about time.
Hey. get back here!
Ow!
Zoe!
No!
Now what?
What are you doing?
Have you ever heard of due process?
What's this? What's going on?
Let us go. bearded man!
-We thought you were chill!
-I am!
If you were.
you'd respect our personal space!
Will you two zip it?
There they are!
I was just on my way to the bathroom.
Is it a bad time?
Out of the way!
Stuffed animal transport coordinator
coming through!
That's not the
stuffed animal transport coordinator!
Open the door!
Open the door now!
That is not the real head of security!
Do not open the door!
Look. you guys figure it out
among yourselves.
Horrible! Horrible!
I haven't felt so humiliated
in my three years of life!
I hope you have a good lawyer!
So that's it?
The kidnapping is over?
I'm not kidnapping you.
I'm saving you!
Saving us? Saving us from what?
What is this place?
What’s with all these...
Cages. cages!
Is this what I think it is...?
Oh no! What have I done now?
Ah!
No!
Guys? Hello?
I'm the guy with the beard.
why aren't you insulting me anymore?
Gordon. Gordon. Gordon...
Everything was going fine
until you stuck your nose in it.
Just wait until people find out
you're experimenting on animals!
The thing is. Gordon
as long as they don't see it.
people don't care.
Now get him!
Come on. guys!
The power's out. whop-dee-doo.
Big problem. huh?
Okay. now that is a big problem. yeah.
Gordon! You are fired!
Fine with me!
Peggy. I've lost Zoe!
I left her at my office. it was easier
for someone else to take care of her
and then she went wild.
and then she bit me
and then she ran away.
And now I don't even know
where she could be.
what her favourite spots are.
I don't even know who her friends are...
I don't even have a recent photo
to show the police!
I'm a terrible father!
Come on in.
A little while ago
I heard a noise and found her in here.
I haven't been able to get her out.
What's wrong with her?
The mutation has taken control of her.
In less than an hour. she'll lose
what little humanity she has left.
Oh. no.
I can’t believe I let this happen.
You let it happen. Gordon?
I caused it all.
Peggy. this is all my fault.
No. Gordon.
If anyone is to blame. I am.
-No. I'm the one to blame.
-I'm much to blame than you are here...
-Zoe. we're such terrible parents.
-Please forgive us.
Huh?
Why are they back to normal?
No idea.
They changed when they saw
what was happening in the lab.
It had to be the fright of their lives.
A fright...
I got it!
Adrenaline! It’s adrenaline!
Yes. of course!
Huh?
Oh. mice of the future.
that’s great.
Have you come up with anything?
When they got frightened.
the animals secreted adrenaline!
And that’s the key we needed
to find to unlock the antidote!
We can save Zoe!
Yeah!
It’s okay. Don't worry. honey.
It won’t hurt a bit.
Hello. friends!
Today we're going to explore...
Works every single time.
the uncertainty principle.
A consequence of quantum formalism...
Hey!
Ouch. Mom!
What? It was the antidote!
And it had to be an injection.
it couldn't be a syrup.
How about thanks and a big hug.
you two?
Thanks.
Sorry to interrupt.
We have reached 3 conclusions.
One: this compound is the origin
of life on Earth.
Two: it is extremely fragile.
so revealing its source
would put the planet in a situation
we have called...
Boom!
And three:
as a civilization you are a disaster.
so. wishing you the best.
we're going as far away as possible.
Goodbye. humans!
He can’t be serious. can he?
Well. well. well...
How interesting!
That’s just the information
that I’m looking for.
Mom. Dad. what's going on?
Zoe. grab your pets.
and get out of here!
What? Why?
Because he wants to puree them!
-Run!
-Hey!
Hey!
You stay away from her!
Get out of our house!
Oh yes. yes...
What you’ve got here
is very interesting...
No.
Is this...
The ultra-complex mutagenic conglomerate
that acts upon genomes by actually
altering their cellular structure.
No. no. no.
It's the motherlode!
The secret to all-powerful DNA.
supreme life energy.
the power of a god.
superanimals. superhumans.
superarmies.
president of the world.
person of the year!
In the Arctic?
Could it be?
Yes! It's real!
It's real!
Here it is!
I found the spark of life
after looking for so long!
Yeah. you found it.
What a creep.
An Exploratron X-99?
I loved those when I was a boy.
And do you know why?
Because they were so basic.
Arctic here I come!
These two know more
than they're letting on.
-so we're taking them with us.
-Don’t touch me!
Bye. bye...
Don't do this. man.
we're friends. aren’t we?
Your name's Gary. isn’t it?
No? It’s not?
Then who is Gary? Is he Gary?
-What about her?
-Leave her here.
There’s nothing special
about her anymore.
No! Let them go!
Go away. brat.
Oh no. Oh no.
Oh. no!
Is anyone here?
If anyone is here.
please know that I am very nervous
and I am not responsible for my actions.
Hey. what’s up?
Oh. no. Zoe!
I broke your lamp!
I'm so sorry.
My head is like a rock.
medical condition.
How did you get in?
Front door was open.
I’ve got your volunteer form right here.
What?
There! You happy?
I guess so... yeah.
It's a strange feeling.
no one has ever signed one.
Is everything okay?
Nothing's okay.
Anything I can do?
I don't know. Kyle.
A tech guru has kidnapped my parents
and taken them to the Arctic
in search of the mutagenic fruits
of an alien plant.
So you tell me what you can do.
Never mind. it's all my fault.
I've done it.
I've messed up so badly
that I'm all alone.
I mean. even my pets are gone.
If you want. we can go find them.
Let them be.
they're better off without me.
You don't seem so bad to me.
Nobody seems bad to you.
And you're not alone
because you're a Greenbuddie.
No offense. but...
What use is that to me now?
This is Kyle McGregor.
volunteer number 3459.
I have an ecological emergency.
Activate the Alpha protocol.
What?
It better be important. I'm missing
pilates because of this call.
Read them and weep: four aces!
Cough up the money.
You're taking advantage
that we don't know how to count!
Making me think.
My brain hurts!
It's impressive to see everything
you've accomplished on your own. madam.
That’s doctor.
Have you ever thought about working
for a private company?
Just think of all the things that
SheetCorp could offer you.
Like unlimited resources.
cutting-edge technology...
And the coffee selection at the bar
is just awesome.
I bet that’s really good.
But I'll wait a bit. in case you
get jail time for kidnapping.
Jail time is for the poor. madam.
I'm sure you know that.
It’s doctor.
Whatever you say.
Hey! Get the mechanic over here.
I think some of the parts
are falling off.
That's not what you think it is.
What's all this noise?
Is a monkey flying this thing or what?
I think it's a marsupial. sir.
You don’t say?
What is that rodent doing in here?
He wants the jellies. sir.
but they’re mine.
No. stop!
Useless furball!
You should have stayed in Australia!
What are you doing!?
Yuck!
Aha! That’s enough!
7000 people on my staff
and I still have to do
everything myself.
Hey?
Oh you snuck in here with a fuzz-bud!
You’re not getting the best of me!
Forget it!
Just leave those lights alone!
When we get home
I’m sending both of you to the zoo!
No. no!
No!
You lousy sticking vermin!
Peggy. we’re alive.
By some miracle.
Sir. we can't locate the animals.
We’re better off without them!
Get the rest of the gear.
You’ll continue on foot.
Come on. everybody up!
And the last time.
I lost all flexibility in my core.
From one week to the next.
boom. gone.
Hey. you listening to me?
Yo. microwave!
I'm opening my heart to you here!
Wow. this microwave
isn’t useless after all.
Okay. we're getting close!
Seat belts! Now!
Are you sure we can land
without this thing falling apart?
Excuse me.
are you a pilot with
thousands of hours of flight time
and decades of experience
in countless extreme rescues?
Ehm... No.
Well then. how about you let me
worry about the landing?
Are you sure you’re related to her?
Uh-huh.
She’s my aunt and my dad's sister.
Both.
Oh my god.
What a pain in the rear.
Well. we’re almost there.
Maybe it’s just a misunderstanding.
I saw my parents get kidnapped.
What’s confusing to you about that?
They could have been kidnapped
by mistake?
Kyle. this may surprise you
but not everyone can be trusted.
You have to set boundaries.
people take advantage of you.
Nobody takes advantage of me!
Really? They do?
-Oh. no!
-Oh. yes.
The sooner you accept it.
the sooner you can start...
Smoke! Over there!
Oh. no!
There's no one inside.
which is a good sign.
What's that? Look!
My pets!
They must have come in the helicopter!
They were super lucky
to survive the accident.
I wouldn’t be surprised
if they caused it.
-Alright. what do we do now?
-How about following those tracks?
Let's go!
Yeah. good idea. Robert. Onward!
I'm just saying we should take turns.
I’m uncomfortable walking backwards
and I feel like I'm missing
the best of the scenery.
Aha!
Wow.
Wow? Wow what?
Hey. hey. hey. hey! Slow down!
Wow.
What's going on?
What is it?
I'm missing out on the good stuff.
aren’t I?
Let me see!
Gordon!
Wow!
Oh my goodness...
the animals have been feeding
on those berries for centuries.
mutating their genes.
That's why they don't migrate.
They mutate.
they’ve adapted to climate change.
From a scientific point of view. it's...
Completely meaningless gibberish?
Exactly.
Although the appropriate
term would be... Magic!
You know?
I'm no expert.
but shouldn't they be eating each other?
Gordon. you're right!
But instead they help one another.
care for each other
and protect each other!
The tree gives them
everything they need.
so they have learned
to trust each other!
That's why adrenaline inhibits
the effects of the berries!
They know no fear!
It's a perfect ecosystem!
Wow.
It's the most beautiful thing
I've ever seen...
I want it for myself.
Cage up the animals.
and sample everything!
Move it!
It's... extraordinary.
The ultimate life energy will be mine!
I’ll have the power of a god!
And it'll look just great
on our rooftop garden!
What? You can't take it!
You'll destroy the ecosystem!
You know that I'm rich. madam.
I can do whatever I want.
Freeze. little bugger!
He's being protective.
he knows they depend on it!
Who. TJ?
No! The walrus bear!
You mean the walrus bear
is protecting TJ?
No! He's protecting the tree from TJ
because they depend on it.
-So the tree depends on TJ?
-Will you just zip it?
I'm missing it because of you!
But of course.
You're missing it!
I don't have time for this junk.
Now you're mine...
Oh...
He wants to protect his little tree.
oh my.
Isn't that simply adorable?
No. it's not.
Stay out of my way.
you ridiculous furry tadpole.
Hashtag save the Arctic.
hashtag biodiversity.
Blah. blah. blah. blah. blah. blah...
He made him cry!
Is he like... a bad person?
Good.
Finally getting it. my nephew.
Oh. I see my parents! There!
Come on. we have to rescue them!
Zoe. wait!
I have so many plans for the two of us.
It's all yours.
No. no. no. no. no. no...
What are you doing?
What's going on here?
Where did all these creatures come from?
Well. like the old saying goes.
if you can't beat 'em. then...
No! That's way. way too much!
Way too much of what?
That's enough.
I need to see what’s going on here.
On second thought... Oop...
Maybe not.
Ha!
I almost missed this because of pilates.
Hey! What are you girls doing here?
Excuse me.
do you have a minute to save the planet?
Can't you see I'm busy?
Calm down!
We're from an environmental organization
fighting to save the planet from...
I already belong to several NGOs!
I can't afford another one!
That's what you always say
and it's always a lie!
Run. Zoe! Save your parents!
Alone?
I think I’ll wait for you!
Robert. no!
Careful. careful. aaahhh!
Come to Daddy.
Huh? Not you again.
Get out of here!
Do you have any idea
who you're messing with. huh?
W-w-w... What?!
This is absolutely the end!
What do you want me to do?
He's a 50-foot monster.
and I'm a 12 year old girl!
Hey!
Robert! Are you alright?
The berries!
Aaahhh...
Are you all thinking what I’m thinking?
Whatever. it can't get any worse.
It’s incredible!
The morphological assimilation
is both immediate and cumulative!
Yes. yes. yes.
very interesting.
but we have to get out of here.
Can't you see that monster
is going to crush us?!
As long as he pays.
that monster can do whatever wants.
Excuse me.
Omega Team. Report.
We found a monkey.
He says he's lost and cold.
A monkey?
A talking monkey?
Affirmative.
He's pretty adorable.
Requesting permission
to lend it a jacke...eeagh!
Omega... Omega Team?
-Get that thing away!
-Report!
What’s going on?
We're under attack!
Aaah!
It's coming!
Release my parents right now.
or else...
Or else what?
Or else...
Uhm. just a second. okay?
Get it. get it!
Come on.
go get it!
Okay. enough of this nonsense.
Huh?
Hey. you. come back here!
Heeey!
Why can't I catch that stupid thing?
Just leave it. don’t worry about it!
Calm down!
I'm fine.
-Zoe!
Did you become an animal again?
What were you thinking?
You can punish her later. no phone!
How did you get here?
We came by plane.
It’s over there!
Whose plane? Do I know them?
Outstanding!
I was starting to worry
about getting home.
Maybe somewhere will be open.
Fancy some sushi?
No!
Don't you remember what the mouse said?
The tree is the source of life!
Just a little more!
We have to stop TJ!
Mom. do you have more of the antidote?
I only have one dose left.
Awesome. You guys go free the animals.
meanwhile you distract TJ.
I'll climb the tree and... aaagh!
Mom! What have you done?
That was the last dose.
You think I’m going to let you
stay an animal forever?
What about the tree?
What do you want us to do?
We don't have anymore antidote!
Aaaaaah!
I have an idea.
but it's dangerous.
I don't have time to explain it.
You have to trust me. alright?
-Yes.
-Sure.
Go for it.
If you think it's a good idea.
so do I.
Zoe...
Try not to mess it up.
I promise you.
Free the animals.
Robert. here we go!
Come on. you have got this... Huh?
-Hey!
-What are you doing here?
Do you actually think
people will love you more
because you're powerful?
That you really have to destroy
everything to get their attention?!
Guess what.
I used to think the same way
but I was wrong.
You don't have to break stuff
and shout louder
if you want attention.
You gotta try to get along with people
You know.
you’re not the only person in the world!
Do you really think
you're going to convince me
with some corny monologue?
No. I just wanted to buy some time.
Some time? Time for what?
Beep.
Oh my. Isn't that simply adorable?
No. it's not.
Stay out of my way.
you ridiculous furry tadpole.
And why should I care?!
We just uploaded that video
to the internet
and I bet you anything it's a huge hit.
And you wanna know why?
Because the world likes
the curious and the kind.
not brutes like you.
Who can talk like that
to something so adorable?
If I get my hands on him.
he'll be sorry!
He's a monster! What a bully!
He's a nobody!
Don't buy his products!
No. no. no. no. no...
No!
Ow. ow. ow!
Zoe! You did it!
You were amazing. sweetheart!
-I am so proud of you!
Yes!
Big hug!
Go on! They’re waiting for you.
Good Luck!
Hey. you. kid.
You gotta help me out here.
This whole thing's
been a total misunderstanding.
I wasn’t trying
to take the tree down. no. no.
I was just trying to move it
so it could get more light.
Oh. really?
Sure. wait until we explain
everything to Zoe.
she'll be so relieved to hear that.
No. no. no. no. no. no. Leave her alone.
What I need is for you
to give me the keys to the plane
for just a minute.
You know. to warm up from the cold.
Sure. of course.
Wow! Hold on...
you're trying to trick me. aren't you?
Eh... No...
Congratulations. nephew.
Looks like you’ve got it.
All I ever wanted to do
is help humanity.
To help us take the next step
in our evolution.
And you still can.
Have you heard of Greenbuddies?
I have something to tell you.
I love you and I want us to get along.
and that's why...
Maybe boarding school
isn't such a bad idea after all.
I could use a little discipline.
Okay honey.
as soon as we see a mailbox.
we'll send in the form.
Robert. can you take care of this?
Mom! What are you...
What do you say we go camping instead?
Or to the beach.
Or camping at the beach.
That's the spirit.
If she wants boarding school.
she can pay for it herself.
Are you thinking what I’m thinking?
-Salvatica.
Zoe. we've decided
we're going to stay here.
Stay here? Are you kidding?
No. We're going to trust our instincts.
Awaken our inner animal.
Defy the the status quo.
Whatever the heck that means.
I don’t know.
But this isn't your habitat.
How are you going to manage?
If we’ve survived life as humans.
we can survive anything.
If you think it's a good idea...
then so do I.
But I'm going to miss you so much.
And we'll miss you.
You can come visit us anytime.
Go on.
Before I get all emotional here.
A FEW WEEKS LATER
That was beyond awful!
Enough roughing it.
what's for dinner?
Tell me you have a charger.
-Dibs on the bathtub!
-Any pizza left?
Blanket and movie!
Wow. this hair needs some conditioner.
Hey there. kiddo.
ready to go?
Oh!
Big hug.
Ready for another beating?
Always!
Your little friends are here?
What happened to back to nature?
Well. maybe...
It just wasn't as cool as they expected.
Oh. poor things...
Anyway. to err is human.
THE END
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm